module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What country was not founded by freed American slaves?', 
      a: 'Sierra Leone', 
      b: 'Haiti',
      c: 'Senegal',
      d: 'Liberia',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of Hawaii\'s islands is known as Pineapple Island ', 
      a: 'Molokai', 
      b: 'Lanai ',
      c: 'Ni\'ihau',
      d: 'Molokini',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many countries does Africa have?', 
      a: '54', 
      b: '89',
      c: '56',
      d: '36',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'In what country to people shake their head for \'yes\' and nod their head for \'no\'?', 
      a: 'Georgia', 
      b: 'Syria',
      c: 'Italy',
      d: 'Bulgaria',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where is the only co-pricincipality (a country run by two princes) in the world?', 
      a: 'Monaco', 
      b: 'Andorra',
      c: 'Liechtenstein',
      d: 'Wales',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the most linguistically diverse country, with over 800 languages spoken?', 
      a: 'Papau New Guinea ', 
      b: 'Tanzania',
      c: 'Peru',
      d: 'India',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What country spans 12 timezones', 
      a: 'France', 
      b: 'China',
      c: 'United States',
      d: 'Russia',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the youngest country in Europe?', 
      a: 'Serbia', 
      b: 'Montenegro',
      c: 'South Sudan',
      d: 'Kosovo',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What country has the record for the highest recorded temperature of 136.4 degrees?', 
      a: 'Tunisia', 
      b: 'Zambia',
      c: 'Libya',
      d: 'South Africa',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What year is it in North Korea? ', 
      a: '109', 
      b: '2020',
      c: '2009',
      d: '120',
      answer: 'a'
    }
  ]
};